Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence and subject files, 1946-2012
  - Subseries 1.1: Chronological files, 1946-2002
    - P general, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - P personal, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Pan Continental Tours, Inc., 1970 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Perilla, Bob, Associates, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Philharmonic Hall - April 5, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - R general, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - R personal, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Radnitz Productions "Little Ark", 1970 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Reprise Records, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - S general, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - S personal, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Howard Samuels, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Screen Actors Guild, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Schlussel, Irwin E., 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Sharon Travel Assoc., 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - T general, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - T personal, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - U general, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - V general, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - WITF-TV (Hershey, Pa.) Williamsburg, Va. show, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - XYZ general, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - XYZ personal, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - A general, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - A personal, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - AFTRA, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - AJC general, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - AJC reception at 25 Bank Street April 13, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - AJC - Nat'l. Commission on Youth, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - AJC Governing Cncl., 1971 (Box 77, Folder 3-4)
    - AJC Executive Committee, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 5-6)
    - AJC Met. Council, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - AJC CJA, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - AJC Chapter Speaking corresp., 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - AJC Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - AJC Hillel & campus groups, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - AJC Search Committee, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Amnesty International, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Amer-Israel Cultural Fdn., 1971 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Auction requests, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - B general, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - B personal, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - J. Bernstein Public Relations, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Bikel, Josef and Miriam, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - 50th Anniversary party April 17, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - C general, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - C personal, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Cinema Center - "City By Night", 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Contracts - correspondence re., 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - D general, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - D personal, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - E general, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - E personal, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - F personal, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - EBM general, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - EBM bills for payment, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - EBM checks for dep., 1971 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - EBM investments, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - EBM oil investments, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Encounter Films, Inc., 1971 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Expense reimbursements, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - F general, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - "Fiddler..." Summer tour, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - "Fiddler..." contracts, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Foster Parents Plan, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Richard Fulton, Inc., 1971 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - G general, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - G personal, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Gildesgame/ Herzliah Inst. luncheon, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - H general, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - H personal, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - I general, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - I personal, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Ionescu, Peter, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - J general, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - J personal, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Jubilee '71, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - K general, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - K personal, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Kaminska Theatre, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - L general, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - L personal, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Luce press clippings, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - M general, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - M personal, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - William Morris Agency, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Wm. Morris Agency - LAX, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - N general, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - N personal, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - New School, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 5-6, Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Newport Folk Festival, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Music Festival, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Nat'l. Jewish Music Cncl., 1971 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - No. American Jewish Students Appeal, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - O general, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Orders - received, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - P personal, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - P general, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - R general, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - R personal, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - S personal, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Screen Actors Guild, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Irwin Schlussel, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Schneider, Richard, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - "Sesame Street", 1971 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - S general, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Silent No More, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 2-4)
    - T general, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - "200 Motels" - Frank Zappa United Artists, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - T personal, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - U general, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - V general, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - W general, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Waldron, Zena, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - W personal, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - XYZ general, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - XYZ personal, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Fan - Fiddler, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Fan mail, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3-4)
    - A general, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - AFTRA, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - AJC general, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 6-7)
    - AJC Chapter Speaking, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - AJC Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - AJC Convention, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - AJC National Biennial Convention, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
    - AJC - Silent No More - post-production correspondence, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - AJC CJA, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - AJC Exec. Committee, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 6-7)
    - AJC Gov. Council, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - AJC Search Committee, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - AJC Hillel & campus grps., 1972 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - AJC Youth Commission, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Amnesty Int'l: reports, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 4-5)
    - Amnesty International, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Auction requests, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - B general, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - B personal, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Bernstein, Jay, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Bikel, Josef & Miriam, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Jacques Brel, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - C general, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - C personal, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Contracts - correspondence re, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Contracts - Rothschilds National Company, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Contracts - Rothschilds Guber Circuit, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Contracts - Jacques Brel, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Contracts - Fiddler Indianapolis, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Contracts - Fiddler Mill Run, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Corp. for Public Broadcasting, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - D general, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - D personal, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Darien House Pub. - Podwal Haggadah, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - E general, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - EBM general, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - EBM checks for deposit, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Encounter Films, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Expense reimbursement, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - F general, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - "Fiddler" - Bikel/Music Fair, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Fund for Higher Education (in Israel) Amnon Barness, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - G general, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - G personal, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - H general, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - H personal, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Herzliah Institute: Josef & Miriam Bikel Scholarship Fund, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - I general, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - I personal, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - J general, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - K general, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - K personal, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - L general, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - L personal, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Lubavitcher, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - "Little Ark", 1972 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Mint, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - M general, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - M personal, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - McGovern campaign, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 5-6)
    - Wm. Morris - NY, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Wm. Morris - Los Angeles, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - N general, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - O general, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Orders received, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - P general, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - P personal, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Q general, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - R general, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - R personal, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - (Fan mail - loose), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 5, Box 91, Folder 1-2)
    - Rothschilds - fan mail, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Rothschilds - Colonie, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Rothschilds - Storrowton, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Rothschilds - Westbury, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Rothschilds - National Company, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - S general, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - S personal, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Screen Actors Guild, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - T personal, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - T general, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - U general, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - V general, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - W general, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - W personal, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Wilton Democratic Town Comm., 1972 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - XYZ general, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - XYZ personal, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - (Loose items), 1972 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - A general, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - A personal, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Ambassador/ Peter Pan, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - AJC general, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - AJC CJA, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - AJC Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - AJC Chapter Speaking, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - AJC Executive Comm., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 1-3)
    - AJC Governing Cncl., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 4-5)
    - AJC Youth Commission, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - AJC "Silent No More", 1973 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - AJC Hillel, & campus groups, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - AJC Arts Chapter, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Amnesty International, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Amnesty Int'l corresp., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Auction requests, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - B personal, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - B general, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - J. Bernstein New York, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - J. Bernstein Los Angeles, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Re: Benja, the King Bremen Dusseldorf, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Bikel, Josef and Miriam, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - C personal, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - C general, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Contracts correspondence re:, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 6-7)
    - Contracts correspondence re:, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - D personal, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - D general, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Expense reimbursement, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Encounter Films, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - E general, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - EMB bills for payment - Bikel, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Fan, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Fund for Higher Education, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Richard Fulton, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - G personal, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - G general, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - H personal, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - H general, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Harry Walker Agency, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - I personal, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - I general, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - speaking, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - concerts, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Israel Yom Kippur War, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 3-4)
    - JWB Lecture Bureau, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - J general, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - K general, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - K personal, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - L general, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - L personal, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - M general, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - M personal, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - "Marriage Go Round" Carillon - Miami Beach, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - "Marriage Go Round" - Dallas, Texas Granny's Dinner Theatre, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Mod Squad - Spelling Productions, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - William Morris - LAX, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - National Jewish Music Cncl., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - No. American Jewish Students Appeal Network, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - N personal, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - N general, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Newport Folk Festival, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Orders - received, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - O general, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Pell, Claiborne Jan. 15, 1973 tribute Providence, RI (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Pan Continental Tours, Inc., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Post-Newsweek Productions "American Immigration", 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - P personal, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - P general, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Q general, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - R personal, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - R general, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - S personal, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - S general, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - T general, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - U general, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - V general, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - W personal, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - W general, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Waldron, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Wilton Democratic Town Committee, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - William Morris - NY, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - XYZ general, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - A general, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - A general, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - AJC Chapter Speaking, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - AJC Convention - NYC Feb. 16-17, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - AJC Arts Chapter, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - AJC Governing Council, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - (AJC unlabeled), 1974 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
    - AJC Commission on Jewish Affairs, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - AJC Hillel & campus groups, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - AJC Youth Commission, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - AJC Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
    - Ambassador/ Peter Pan Records, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Amnesty Int'l - correspondence, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Amnesty Int'l reports, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 6, Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Auction requests, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - B personal, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - B general, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Jay Bernstein - NY office, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Bikel - 50th birthday messages, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Bikel, Josef & Miriam, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - "Jacques Brel...", 1974 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Brel... Valley Forge (Dec. 3-8, 1974) Westbury (Dec. 10-22, 1974) (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - C personal, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - C general, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Comm. to Combat Huntington's Disease, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Contracts - correspondence, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
    - D general, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - D personal, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - E general, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Expense reimbursements, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - EBM general, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - EMB - bills for payment, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - EMB - checks for dep., 1974 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - EMB - investments, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - EBM - oil investments, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - F general, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - F personal, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - "Fiddler..." Latin Casino, Camden, NJ, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Fund for Higher Education, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - G general, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - G personal, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - H general, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - H personal, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - I general, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - "I Do, I Do" - Carillon/ Miami, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries - lectures, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries - concerts, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - J general, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - JWB Lecture Bureau, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - K general, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - K personal, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Mr. Kelly's - Chicago, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - L general, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - L personal, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - M personal, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - M general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - N personal, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - N general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Nat'l. Jewish Music Cncl., 1974 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Orders received, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - O personal, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - P general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Pan Continental Tours, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Q general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - R general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - R personal, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - S general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - S personal, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - St. Regis - Maisonette April 16-27, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - "Sunshine Boys" - Coconut Grove 12/25/73 - 1/13/74, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - T general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - T personal, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Tiffany Communications Bureau (Ben Bernstein), 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Takas, William, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - U general, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - UJA/ Israel Oct. 10-19, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - V general, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - V personal, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - W personal, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - W general, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Wm. Morris - NY (completed), 1974 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Wm. Morris - LAX, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Harry Walker Agency, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Wilton Dem. Town Comm., 1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Waldron, Rosina, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - XYZ general, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - XYZ personal, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - A - Z Fan, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 6, Box 106, Folder 1)
    - (Letters sent), 1974 (Box 106, Folder 2-4)
    - A general, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - A fan, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - A personal, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - AFTRA, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Ambassador/ Peter Pan, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - AJC general, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - AJC Chapter Speaking, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - AJC Comm. on Jewish Affairs, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - AJC Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - AJC Governing Council, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - AJC Youth Commission, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - AJC Hillel & campus groups, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Amnesty Int'l - correspondence, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Amnesty Int'l reports, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 4-5)
    - Auction requests, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - B general, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - B personal, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - B fan, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Black Americans to Support Israel Committee, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - J. Bernstein - LAX office, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - J. Bernstein - NY office, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Bikel, Josef & Miriam, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - C general, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - C fan, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - C personal, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Committee - Huntington's Disease, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Contracts, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Concert correspondence - #2 Fall/Winter, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Contracts fee pending, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Contracts tech. notes, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Contract correspondence dates completed, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 5-7, Box 109, Folder 1)
    - D general, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - D personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - D fan, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Drive Your Car Service, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - E general, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - E personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - E fan, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - F general, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - F personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - F fan, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - G fan, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - G personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - G general, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - H personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - H fan, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - H general, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - I personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - I general, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries - television, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries - plays, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Inquiries - lectures, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Inquiries - concerts, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - J fan, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - J personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - J general, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - JWB Lecture Bureau, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - K personal, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - K general, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - K fan, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - L personal, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - L general, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - L fan, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - M personal, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - M fan, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - M general, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Wm. Morris - NY, pending, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Wm. Morris - completed, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Wm. Morris - LAX, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - N personal, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - N fan, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - N general, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - R personal, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - S fan, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Tiffany Communications, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Herb Tobias, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Wm. Takas, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Unused tickets, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Unsolicited music, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - U general, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - UNESCO protest - Schubert Theatre, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - V general, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - V personal, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - W general, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - H. Walker Agency, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - W fan, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - W personal, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - XYZ personal, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - XYZ general, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - XYZ fan, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - (Letters sent), 1975 (Box 111, Folder 5-6)
    - (A - loose), 1976 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - A general, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - A personal, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - A fan, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - AFTRA, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - AJC general, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - AJC - Congressional replies to letter re: Rabbi Gordis, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - AJC Executive Comm., 1976 (Box 112, Folder 3)